# **ASHISH PANDEY**

### Assistant Vice President, Business Development

ashishpandey.9@gmail.com | +91 9573616871 | 203, Prashsan Nagar, Jubilee Hills, Hyderabad.

## **PROFILE**

12 years of hands-on experience in the areas of Corporate Sales, B2B/SaaS Sales, Business Development, Alliances and Partnerships. With exposure across IT Healthcare, Finance, Digital Payments and Telecom, have managed large teams to deliver projects and goals across sectors. Have excelled in client facing roles, managed P&L & business expansion.

## **EDUCATION**

MBA - Marketing, ICFAI Business School, Hyderabad

May 2008 - Apr 2010

B. Tech - Computer Science, Osmania University, Hyderabad

Apr 2004 - May 2008

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### Assistant Vice President, Ekincare, Hyderabad

Mar 2021 - Present

- Responsible for revenue growth, new accounts, pricing and profitability for enterprise and mid-market business.
- Plan and execute strategic initiatives to drive platform adoption and SaaS revenue.
- Achieved 3X (45Cr) revenue growth in a span of 12 months through acquisition of over 50 accounts.
- Attract, enable and retain a highly motivated sales team that prides on achieving goals.
- · Liaise with product, customer success and marketing to enhance customer experience.

#### Head of Sales/Consultant, Mfine, Hyderabad

Jul 2019 - March 2021

- Spearheading the go-to-market strategy for Hyderabad and Mumbai region and managing the corporate sales business for these markets, resulting in revenue growth of ₹10 Mn in Q3 & Q4 FY 19-20.
- Securing business by maintaining top accounts and strategizing innovative healthcare solutions to accomplish business objectives.
- Promoting Mfine's on-demand digital primary health care platform and services to clients. Liaising with insurance companies and insurance brokers to introduce new products and improve market presence.

#### Regional Sales Manager, American Express, Hyderabad

May 2015 - Jul 2019

- Responsible for driving consumer card & corporate payments business for the location through a large team.
- Created a distinct sales plan for sales managers and account executives to follow.
- Ensured all performance standards are met viz. sales results, business targets, controls and compliance & people development. Consistently
- achieved over 100% targets, with an average achievement of 130%. Was promoted twice in the process

# Sales Manager, Airtel, Hyderabad

Feb 2014 - May 2015

- Managed 4 sales channels with over 40 employees for mobile business in and around Hyderabad.
- Acquired over 100 small and medium corporate businesses and ensured maximum product penetration.
- Exceeded targets each quarter with average achievement of 150% for the year 14-15.

### Senior Relationship Manager, ICICI Bank Limited, Bangalore

Jul 2012 - Jul 2013

- With a team of over 12 privilege bankers, managed a book size of over 200 Cr and 2000 wealth & privilege banking clients across Bangalore
  city.
- Portfolio Management assets, liabilities and insurance products.

### Banking Executive, Citibank, Hyderabad

Sep 2010 - Jan 2012

· Sales to high net worth clients, primarily credit cards and accounts.

## **SKILLS**

| Business development | B2B/SAAS Sales  |
|----------------------|-----------------|
|                      |                 |
| Account Management   | Team Management |